Bui Huy Tung - Blockchain Developer

Phone: 0913115560 / Email: huytung139@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Blockchain Developer with **more than 2 years** of experience in Ethereum-based Blockchain and Solana Blockchain combined with **3 years** working as **Software Engineer**. My ambition is to offer customers high-quality software with the most convenient and good quality product.

With a big passion for technology and the honor want to create many easy & convenient products to resolve problems in life so I usually spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better engineer that I'm able to give and create professional solutions.

SKILL

Blockchain	Solidity, Chainlink, Truffle, Hardhat, Moralis, Infura, Near SDK; Understanding PoW, PoS, PoH, PoA, EVM, Yield Farming; Experienced in Marketplace, Lottery, Lending-Renting NFT, Auction, etc; Solana, Rust, Anchor, cNFT, xNFT, Helius, etc.
JavaScript	ReactJS, NextJS, EJS, Vite, React Native, Redux, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MQTT, SocketlO, web-socket stream, Azure Functions, Azure Static Web Apps, serverless etc.
Dart	Flutter
CSS	Chakra UI, Antd, Rsuite, Material UI, Reactstrap, Less, SASS/SCSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, etc.
Python	Pandas, Numpy, OpenCV 2, Flask API
Database	MongoDB, mySQL, postgreSQL, SQL Server, Azure CosmosDB
Management	IT mentor, Team leadership
Others	Firebase SDK, Facebook SDK, Azure PlayFab, MoMo payment service, VNPay payment service, Zalo Notification Service SDK, Zalo Mini App SDK, etc. Hands-on setting up pipeline on Github/Gitlab, automatic deploying script.

ACHIEVEMENT

- Winning 1st prize at Tool For Idea 3 times continuously.
- Placed in top 10 at the Grizzlython hackathon of Solana at Web3 Space.
- Top 2 at the Hack 08 of Solana Super Team Vietnam.
- Placed in the top 20 at the Hyperdrive global hackathon contest of Solana in the Game & Entertainment section.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

❖ Relipa CO., LTD

OCT 2022 - PRESENT

Blockchain Developer

- Hands-on setting up pipeline on Gitlab, doing multitask well by holding 4-5 projects.
- Participating in blockchain development: DEFI, ecosystem, Layer-2 projects.
- Achievement: making 1 project from having negative turnover to on-time deliverable, continuously receiving compliments and positive feedback from customers in 2 projects continuously, bringing turnover of project over 3 man-months.

❖ Toriti Limited

AUG 2020 – JUL 2023

Software Engineer

- R&D confused business features and new technologies
- Training, supporting, and ensuring progress, quality of work in order to build a efficient team in work.
- Improving sense of responsibility and other soft skills in work, experienced in remote working.

Oasys (7 members)

FEB 2022 - PRESENT

Relipa

• **Description:** Oasys is a new blockchain network in Japan, and it contains many Layer-2 verses. It in progress of building explorer website & creating service on AWS to operate system.

• Technologies:

- o Front-end: NextJS, Material UI, Typescript, etc.
- Back-end: AWS Lambda Function (serverless), postgreSQL, Jest, Typescript, etc.
- Third-party and others: ethersJS

• Responsibilities:

- Research & clarify business of complicated features to help members understand clearly and actively contribute to the functionality of the feature which improves working progress faster than 40%.
- o Implement difficult tasks: verifying smart contract, optimizing long SQL statement, etc.
- Participating in writing scripts to synchronize millions of records of the blockchain database and RPC.
- Hands-on AWS EC2, Lambda, IAM, Cloud Watch, Load Balancer, ACM, Target group, etc.

❖ Win DAO (10 members)

JAN 2022 - OCT 2022

Onsite C2i

- **Description:** A DAO ecosystem project containing lots of fascinating features: NFT mining, token staking, NFT lottery, token lottery, NFT auction, NFT swapping, NFT marketplace, DAO voting, etc
- Technologies:
 - o Front-end: ReactJS & Redux, Ant-design
 - o Back-end: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB
 - o Smart Contract: Solidity, Truffle, Openzeppelin
 - o Third-party and others: Wallet Connect, Metamask, Moralis, Infura, ethersJS

Responsibilities:

- Communicate with team & stakeholders to clarify project requirements and advise business of features.
- Reviewing code & mentoring new members in the team to ensure code quality.
- o Implement full features (smart contract, back-end, front-end): staking, mining, auction, market place, NFT lottery, token lottery.

❖ Vietnam vehicle registration center software (15 members)

AUG 2021 – JUL 2023

Toriti Limited

• **Description:** A solution for vehicle registration and inspection center. This application is going to be used by people all over Vietnam. **over 10,000** users joining each month.

• Technologies:

- o Front-end: ReactJS & Redux, Ant-design, etc.
- o Back-end: NodeJS, Hapi, mySQL, web-socket stream, Joi validation, Mocha etc.
- Third-party and others: Firebase Cloud Messaging, MQTT, Stringee, Zalo Notification Service, Zalo Mini App, etc.

• Responsibilities:

- Participating in designing database schema and implementing back-end services for this app.
- o Implement additional functionalities (both back-end and front-end) based on the requirement and stakeholders.
- Responsible for work with related-parties to integrate Trung tam dang kiem's system with theirs like: MoMo, VNPay, Zalo, FCM etc.
- Set up pipeline, script: deploying Zalo Mini App which improves working progress better than 20%, ...

Payment Gateway

JUN 2022 - SEP 2022

Owner

- **Description:** This software allows users to pay the bill using ERC20 token or native token instead of using normal smart banking. It is a third party that is able to automatically handle orders. It is inspired by products VNPay, MoMo. Currently, Metamask and TRON Link are supported.
- Technologies:
 - Front-end: ReactJS, Antd.

- Back-end: NodeJS, Hapi, mySQL, Knex, etc.
- Third party and others: Metmask, TRON Link, ethersJS, Infura, Firebase Cloud Messaging, etc.

Q-Traffic (6 members)

JUN 2022 - OCT 2022

Onsite C2i

• **Description:** A simple website which is used for advertising and rental the transportation solution product.

• Responsibilities:

- Define the architecture, coding convention, code-base for all repositories (front-end, back-end, linter, unit-test, build script).
- Communicate with the customer to generate product roadmap and requirements. Giving
 estimation to the items on the product roadmap, turning them into actionable work tickets, and
 assigning them to members of my team.
- o Holding daily meetings, managing tasks and tracking the project progress using management applications to ensure project development is always at good.

Technologies:

- o Front-end: ReactJS & Redux, Typescript, Tailwind, etc.
- o Back-end: NodeJS, Hapi, mySQL, SQL Server, Sequelize, Mocha,.
- Third-party and others: Firebase authentication.

Fihome (11 members)

DEC 2021 - MAR 2022

Toriti Limited

- **Description:** A real estate agency platform website. It allows user, real estate agents to post real estate for sale. The website provides many utilities that help users find real estate easily.
- Responsibilities:
 - Holding daily meetings to track progress of front-end development.
 - Implement important sections of front-end application. Reviewing code & mentoring new members.
 - o Participating in designing database schema and implementing back-end services for this app.

Technologies:

- o Front-end: NextJS, ReactJS & Redux, Typescript, Ant-design, etc.
- o Back-end: NodeJS, Hapi, mySQL, SQL Server, Sequelize, Mocha,.
- Third-party and others: Firebase authentication, Firebase Cloud Messaging, MoMo, etc.

Toppan NFT - NFT mining and transferring web application Relipa	OCT 2022 – FEB 2023
Forex Trading – Centralized Exchange web app Toriti Limited	OCT 2022 – MAR 2023

EDUCATION

Thang Long University

AUG 2020 - AUG 2023

Majority: Information Technology

- Got a scholarship at the first year.
- Toeic score: 750 / 990.
- Graduated in only 3 years (earlier than standard 1 year) with the Good bachelor's degree.